Hi, and this last one, I'll explain you how to work the most popular pilot mode, which
called the "Agent Mode".
So, you can enable it to switch to that mode right here, from the dropdown.
But if you don't see this dropdown, it might be the reasons.
The first use to Alt with those to the code version, you can check on your code menu
and about with those to the code, and you will see the version right here.
So if you use version 1.99 or later, you will have this feature.
If you use the older version, you won't have it.
But if you still don't see an "Agent Mode" right here, it might be a need to enable it
in a settings.
You can go to the settings, and you can chart the fine by option chart dot agent dot enabled,
you can either see the option, so you should check this agent and it will enable the
app pilot.
And then you can choose it right here.
Okay.
You can use "Agent Mode" to start some autonomous coding workflow, compile it, view, figure
out a needed context and file, so you shouldn't choose the context from here, you
know, shouldn't choose any file, so it will figure out everything for you.
If you identify the required tasks, the requirements, the method options can need to use
just to reach the goal you set him via prompt.
So let's go through some use cases for the "Agent Mode".
You can use it for a bigger factor in your code.
For example, if you need to refactor a few files, or you need to refactor a big part of
your application, like you need to use some particular library, in your application, you
can ask to do it and it will change it over multiple files.
So you can also ask, like, if you want to plan an implement in new features, like you need
to add some login form, where you need to add some pages to your application, you can
also ask it, for example, you need to add login form using this particular authentication
library to your project is kind of heavy task and compile it, "Agent Mode" can do it
for you.
You can also migrate to a new setup, like if you use some class components, you can
ask you to write your components from class to functional one, if you have a lot of components,
you also need to be careful because compile it might be also do some mistakes, so you
can miss some components should be updated, and it's always your responsibility to be
sure it provides an extra result, you apply it also needed changes to make the application
work.
You can also generate some task plan, like if you need to create a do application using
the React, to redox state management, and next task for the backend, you can ask a pilot
a key, give me step-by-step guide what I need to do to implement it.
You can also define however requirements for some functional quantities, for example, we need
to implement, for God's path for functionality for your block, and you don't know all the
details how it should be implemented, what use cases you need to cover, and you can ask
a pilot to find requirements, and if you explain your step-by-step, what should be covered,
and also provide you some ideas or implementations, okay, let's now play a bit with
scope pilot, agent mode, so, let's first start with some refactoring, and we use native
data plus to work with this, and for example, I want to use a digest library, popular library
for working with dates, and I want to ask a pilot to work with it, I just close all the files
so you don't know in which file you need to update it, and let's ask, use digest library
to work with dates, let's see, so, of course, he suggests us to run the command to install
the digest library, I hopefully continue, and you'll see we have the mod models folder
where all the dependencies are installed, we have also the package.walkanddoc.json,
files where all the dependencies mentioned, and we also see the updated digest file where
we use digest library, so we can just keep and use it, okay, now let's ask something
more complex, I will start a new chart because it will be a different question, so,
over all the project files, maybe not all the project cover, date and calculator class, we
are unit tests, let's see how it will do it, so, he's syncing, okay, he found the date
file, he added some tests, you see his date you deal, and he does some checks, okay, he
checks that it initializes with custom date, as add function works, correct, subtract
work correctly, and also, it works in a chain, okay, and also he did it for calculator
class as well, so we see unit tests have been generated, I'll just click keep, okay,
so let's ask, maybe, I will close all the files, might be something more difficult, like
I'll start a new chart, for example, we want to add, I don't know, a cover, yep, make
that option, add to make buttons blue and red, and cover it by tests, let's see how it
will implement it, he will need to create some files, some CSS file, okay, he did it to be
a props, and we don't like it, so we will ask to do it with the CSS, implement covers
via CSS, and user should be able to pass cover via props, let's see how it will solve
this task, okay, we see created buttons dot CSS file, so we have to plus button blue and
button red, we have button, where we can pass the cover, I guess he's still updating
the file, okay, he's deciding what classes to pass right here, and also in tests, we
check that if we pass the blue cover, okay, we check the class name, button blue and button
red, as you see it can work with different tasks, okay, you're un-sectated button test
to ensure, yeah, he also just runs a test, just check everything works, yeah, everything
works, everything's fine, so as you can see, compile it, agent mode can work with more
complex tasks, you even shouldn't mention the context, you can just explain what you want
to implement and do it, but as you solve this example with buttons, you need to, my specify
more detailed prompt, if you wanna do what you expect from the first attempt, we can
also keep everything right here, okay, now let's go through like difference between edit
mode and compile and agent mode, edit and agent mode, and there are some use cases when
the edit mode is might be better to use rather than compile it, agent mode, so when it
switched to the next shot, the chat session will be removed, you can back to it, so, okay,
the first use case, the edit mode, for example, if you need to process some simple changes
like you, you know, it's one of few files, you can of course use an edit mode, it will
be less resources and less, like if you have some limitations of your compiler, like right
here, so you can use better some edit mode that you'll use rest, less tokens, less requests
to the back end, for example, also, if you need to implement something simple like, you
know, in what files, you can ask edit mode, it can do it faster, for example, because
agent mode sometimes can do a lot of requests to the back end, some manipulation, and it
can take longer, also, for example, the request request quota, yeah, like an agent mode,
as it all like, depending of course on your past complexity, one prompt might result in many
requests to the back end, which will use more quotas of your account,